<resources>
    <string name="integer">%d</string>
    <string name="app_name">Pixel Sprite Maker</string>

    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="random_all">Randomize All</string>
    <string name="refresh">Generate</string>
    <string name="batch">Save Batch</string>

    <string name="batch_title">Batch size</string>
    <string name="batch_hint">Number of images to save</string>

    <string name="width_hint">Width (px)</string>
    <string name="height_hint">Height (px)</string>
    <string name="cross">x</string>

    <string name="seed_label">Seed</string>
    <string name="random_seed">Random</string>
    <string name="randomize">Randomize</string>

    <string name="center_density">Center density</string>
    <string name="edge_density">Edge density</string>
    <string name="bias">Bias</string>
    <string name="gain">Gain</string>
    <string name="mirror_x">Horizontal Mirror</string>
    <string name="mirror_y">Vertical Mirror</string>
    <string name="mirror_p">Positive Mirror</string>
    <string name="mirror_n">Negative Mirror</string>

    <string name="num_colors"># Colors</string>
    <string name="num_seeds"># Seed Pts</string>

    <string name="color_speed">Color Speed</string>
    <string name="color_mutation">Mutation</string>

    <string name="color_select">Base Color</string>
    <string name="color_hue">Hue</string>
    <string name="color_sat">Sat</string>
    <string name="color_val">Val</string>
    <string name="color_preview">Color Preview</string>

    <string name="preview_Desc">Generated sprite</string>

    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="source">Goto Source Code</string>

    <string name="explanation">Pixel Sprite Maker will randomly generate pixel art sprites that you can customize!\n
The "Seed" input is a magic number that works as a starting point for all random operations. Changing this value gives you different random outcomes for the same parameters.\n
Checking the "Random" seed box will choose a new seed every time a new image is generated. The "Randomize" button will also create a new random seed. If you want, you can manually input your own seed.\n
The "Edge" and "Center" densities are the likelihoods of a pixel in the edge and center, respectively, being filled in.\n
"Bias" and "Gain" skew these probabilities toward or away from the center and midpoints of the image.\n
The probability of the image being mirrored on the x-axis, y-axis, and positive and negative diagonals can be adjusted.\n
"Color speed" is the rate at which seeded random colors fill in. A higher color speed gives a more uniformly colored sprite.\n
"Mutation" is the likelihood of  pixel being uniquely colored apart from its neighbors.\n
Each seed point is a starting point in the image for a random color, picked from a randomly generated palette.\n
You can use "Base color" to control a base or thematic color for the palette, or allow it to be chosen randomly.\n
"Despeckle" is the likelihood of a pixel with no neighbors being cleared.\n
"Despur" is the likelihood of a pixel with 1 neighbor being cleared.\n
"Relax" is the likelihood of a pixel with 7 neighbors being filled.\n
"Devoid" is the likelihood of a pixel with 8 neighbors being filled.\n
"Randomize All" will randomly select nearly all parameters and generate a new image.\n
"Generate" will only update the seed and color if they are set to random, and will create the image for the given parameters.\n
Hit the Generate button to create an image that matches your specified parameters.\n
Saving a batch generates a series of images and saves them all to your gallery.\n
Feel free to goto the source code from the menu to see the internal workings for yourself!
    </string>

    <string-array name="ca_choices">
        <item>Despeckle</item>
        <item>Despur</item>
        <item>Relax</item>
        <item>Devoid</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>